### MAYURESH BADGUJAR

CERTIFIED SNOWFLAKE + SAP HANA 2.0 + BW4HANA 2.0

Working experience at Munich, Germany

~8 Years

+91-9175423681 badgujarmp@gmail.com

LinkedIn URL PAN - India

DOB - 22/07/1993

## **Profile**

~8 years of experience in BI + Cloud analytics with Retail, manufacturing and reinsurance business. Working with cloud analytics technologies on ETL, ELT, Modelling, Reporting and Data Analysis. Working on client facing role in agile methodology on Onshore + Offshore delivery model. Experience of Architect, Design, Team lead, SME, Developer, Migration, Release and Rollouts.

## Certifications

1. SAP HANA 2.0

3. SQL

5. Google Data Analytics

7. Data Analysis

9. Snowflake all Batches completed

2. SAP BW4HANA 2.0

4. Python

6. Power BI

8. Data Visualization

10. Azure AZ-900 (Cloud)

## Experience

07.2022 -Current date

#### Sr. BI Consultant at LPDG, India

Working in agile mode as Cloud analytics BI consultant on Data Analytics role. I am responsible for requirement gathering, solution providing, creation of technical document, architect, design, development, POC, and release-rollout. Working on Cloud technologies like Snowflake and Azure data factory and SAP BW, SAP BWONHANA, SAPERP and, S/4HANA technologies.

02.2021 -06-2022

#### Sr. BI Consultant at Infosys Technology Limited, India

Responsibilities of Design, Development and releases in SAP BI project. Worked on client facing role to take requirements, convert into technical document, optimization and work with cross functional teams. Worked on SAP Native HANA, SQL, SQL server and AFO.

I was leading the team of 10 members. Worked in agile methodology to provided estimations of tasks, taking part in planning meetings, setup and groom the new resources in team.

09.2015 -01.2021

#### BI Consultant at Capgemini Technology Services India Ltd

Sr. Developer for SAP BI application (Native HANA, BWonHANA, SQL,AMDP, SQL server, AFO). Worked on client facing role, take part in release and rollouts. Worked on ETL, reporting, modelling, migrating objects, delivering the tasks and providing trainings.

Provided solutions and suggestions in project, supporting new resource to enhance their skills needed for project. Worked and learn the agile way of working.

Skills

Programming Languages: SQL, Python, ABAP, AMDP and HTML

Database : SAP HANA, SQL Server, SAP ECC, S4HANA, Snowflake **ETL** : SDA- SDI, Azure data factory (ADF), BODS (beginner level)

: AFO, Power BI and SAC(Beginner). Reporting

**Tools** : Eclipse, HANA studio, Toad, SQL server studio, Excel, Power Point and

Microsoft word

**Soft Skills** : Communication, Critical thinking, Problem solving and Public speaking.

## Education

06.2011 -05.2015

#### **Bachelor of Engineering**

Stream: Electronics and Telecommunications

College: Sinhgad Institute of Technology, Lonavala, Pune

06.2010 -

05.2011

#### HHC (12th Grade)

Stream: Science (Major Math, Physics and Chemistry)

College: R.C.Patel Jr. College, Shirpur, Dhule

## **Projects**

#### 07.2022 – Current date

#### **Plant Hub Data - Cloud data Integration**

Technology – Snowflake, Azure, SQL, SAP ECC, S/4Hana and BWonHANA.

Client - Tesa

Role - Architect/Design / SME / Sr. Developer

- It's purely cloud analytics project, where goal is to optimize/monitor the machine cost and increase the productivity of manufacturing.
- The source of data is in SAP + 4 more systems, SQL servers and Pricing API, where Azure is used as an integration tool and snowflake is for cloud data warehousing. Reporting is done in power bi tool.
- I am Responsible for Architect, Design, requirement gathering, presale activities, POC, development, SME and release-rollout of SAP Data integration.
- I am writing the ABAP based functional module in SAP ERP, creation of CDS view in S/4HANA and writing SQL script to meet the business requirement.
- Creating the pipeline in azure data factory (ADF) to pull the data from sap and sql server and then load
  into snowflake database. Worked on the SAP CDC and SAP table connector.
- Created database, schema, SQL script, views, snow pipes and tables in snowflake.
- I am doing the release of objects from dev to production and monitoring the daily activities of sap, ADF and snowflake.
- Providing the solution of technologies, performing business analysis and successfully done the POC.

# 02.2021 **–** 07-2022

#### Supply and Demand Forecasting

Technology - SAP HANA 2.0, SQL, BODS, SQL Server and AFO.

Client - Intel.

Role - Team Lead / Design / Sr. Developer

- Managed a team of 10 members, Responsible for Native HANA deliverables, managed to handle critical releases single headedly.
- Taking a requirement from client and created design of development model, presented result of development to product owner and businesspeople.
- Worked with cross functional teams/leads to assure the standard of projects and to follow the common architecture. It helped to maintain the harmony of project and reduce the maintenance cost.
- Worked in agile methodology were planning the release, iterations and sprints. Responsible for assigning task and making sure team has completed them within time.
- Optimizing the solution and accountable for performance tuning, it ran the project smooth and stable.
- Modelling and developing complex model with Calculation view, SQL scripts, table functions and procedures.
- I have built 3 resources for project and got the billing for them.

#### 09.2015 – 01.2021

#### **EDWH – Pricing and Combine Reporting**

Technology - SAP BWonHANA, SAP HANA 2.0, SQL, SLT, SDI-SDA and AFO.

Client - Munich Re

Role - Developer / Sr. Developer

- Responsible for SAP Native HANA + BWHANA deliverables. Worked as Developer and Sr.Developer.
- Directly communicating with Business analyst and architecture to understand the requirement and do the modelling and reporting within SAP HANA.
- Developed the model in Native HANA using Calculation views, SQL scripts, table functions and procedures.
- Worked on BWonHANA artefacts Data Source, AMDP, DTP, Transformation, ADSO, Info-objects and Composite provider.
- Created the BEX queries in Eclipse to meet the business reporting requirement. Built the Complex query for business reporting on Actual vs Expected data.
- Worked on hybrid approach Native HANA + BWonHANA, to have real time reporting and also history data analysis.
- Developed the AFO workbook, also did the automation with AFO to check the quality of data between Production and shadow environments.

## Languages

• English, Marathi, Hindi and Learning A1 level German language.